《生活大爆炸》  前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
猜我在洛杉矶机场发现谁了  我的妹妹普丽娅
Guess who I found at LAX. My baby sister Priya.
真高兴再次见到你 莱纳德
It's really nice to see you again, Leonard.
恩  我也很高兴见到你
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
到了
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
-你上了我妹妹  -对
- You slept with my sister?! - Yeah.
这是对我信任莫大的背叛
This is a terrible betrayal of my trust!
要是我告诉你
Would it help if I told you
我向她献出真心
that I offered her my heart,
却被她狠狠践踏  你会好受点么
and she kinda stomped on it?!
她践踏得多狠
How hard did she stomp?
相当狠
Very hard.
好吧  好受多了
Okay, I'm good.
什么事那么好笑
What's so funny?
没什么  只是在想
Nothing. Just thinking
人做爱时发出的声音
about the noises people make during sex.
我有时确实有点不能自已  是吧
I do sometimes get a bit carried away, don't I?
很可爱
It's cute.
听起来像只喝醉的猴子
You sound a little like a drunken monkey.
你懂的  那其实是对你的赞美
You know it's meant as a compliment.
我也是这么理解的
That's how I take it.
太完美了
This is perfect.
真希望这一刻永远停留
I hope this moment never ends.
我也是
Me, too.
噢  该走了
Well, gotta go. Oh!
这么快  留下来过夜吧
Already? Why don't you stay over?
我也想  但是你知道
I'd love to, but you know
我妈早上需要我
my mother needs me in the morning.
拜托  我认为她能
Please. I think the woman can manage
自己戴假发
to put a wig on by herself.
不仅仅是假发
It's not just the wig.
还要把她的头发盘起来  画眉毛
It's pinning her hair up, drawing on her eyebrows.
是两个人才能干的活儿
It's a two-person job.
只是  我们刚做完爱你就走
It's just, when you leave right after we make love,
让我觉得自己
it makes me feel...
很贱
cheap.
亲爱的  对不起
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
我能做什么呢
What can I do?
留下来
Stay.
好吧
Okay.
再待个五分  十分钟吗
Like, what, another five, ten minutes?
回家吧
Go home.
听你的
Your call.
霍华德
Howard...
你有考虑过一起住吗
have you ever considered us living together?
天啊  我不知道
Boy, I don't know.
你  我  妈住在同一屋檐下
You, me, Ma living under the same roof?
不是  我是说只有你和我
No, I mean just you and me.
你可以搬过来
You can move in here,
或者我们另找个住处
or we can find a place.
-我有个更好的主意 -什么
- I've got a better solution. - What?
我妈吃那么多盐  心脏早晚受不了
We wait for my mom's heart to explode
我们等她心脏崩溃
from all the salt she eats.
把她埋进土里  把她的床垫翻个面儿
Then we just stick her in the ground, flip her mattress
搬进大卧室
and move into the big bedroom.
很好
Great.
看看我们  在一起规划未来啦
Look at us planning a future together!
是谁
Who's there?!
是性侵者吗
Are you a sex criminal?!
性侵者没有钥匙  妈
Sex criminals don't have keys, Ma!
这么晚你到哪儿去了
Where were you so late?!
我和伯纳黛特出去了
I was out with Bernadette!
我知道那是什么意思
I know what that means!
我看《菲尔博士》
I watch Dr. Phil!
美国脱口秀节目
希望上帝保佑  但愿你用避孕套了
I hope to God you used a condom!
我不跟你谈这个话题  妈
I'm not having this conversation with you, Ma!
上帝保佑你不会得个什么新型怪性病
God forbid you get one of those new fancy sex diseases!
没人有病
Nobody has a disease!
希望如此
I hope not!
我跟你共用一个厕所呢
I share a toilet with you!
那就是你想的吗
Is that what you want?!
想让你妈妈得上疱疹吗
To give your mother herpes?!
够啦  我受够啦
That's it! I don't have to take this!
祝你早上画眉毛顺利
Good luck with your eyebrows in the morning!
是谁
Who's there?!
你是性侵者吗
Are you a sex criminal?!
我还没走
I'm still leaving!
我忘拿我的克敏能了
I just forgot my Claritin!
含氯雷他定 抗过敏药物
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧原创翻译 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：MADD  乖乖的韩小仙  joanna  YY
后期：孤帆    时间轴：小e
■
校对：空虚的VV      总监：郁闷的YY
生活大爆炸第四季第十六集
什么事
Hey, what's up?
需要个住的地方
I need a place to crash.
当然
Uh, sure.
为什么
Why?
跟我妈大吵一架
Big fight with my mother.
还在争哪部《犯罪现场调查》最棒吗
Still arguing over which CSI is the best?
不是  我们一致同意它们各有千秋
No, we agreed they all have their merits.
是关于伯纳黛特
This was about Bernadette.
怎么了
What's going on?
霍华德今晚要在这睡
Howard's gonna sleep here tonight.
他跟他妈吵架了
He had a fight with his mother.
你给他上热饮了吗
Did you offer him a hot beverage?
没
No.
莱纳德  社交礼仪规定  如果朋友心情不好
Leonard, social protocol states when a friend is upset,
你应该给他们倒杯热饮  比如茶
you offer them a hot beverage, such as tea.
茶听起来是不错
Tea does sound nice.
你听见他的话了  莱纳德
You heard the man, Leonard.
与此同时  我也心情不好
And while you're at it, I'm upset
因为来了一位不速之客  所以给我一杯可可
that we have an unannounced houseguest, so make me cocoa.
有个问题
Point of inquiry,
既然莱纳德是你的第二好友
given that Leonard is your secondary friend
库萨帕里才是你的头号好友
and Koothrappali is your primary friend,
你为什么没去他那
why didn't you seek refuge under his roof?
没地方
There's no room.
他妹妹住在他家
His sister is staying with him.
等等  等等  什么
Wait, wait. What?
可可  莱纳德  集中精力
Cocoa, Leonard. Focus.
我现在很郁闷
I'm down in the dumps here.
普丽娅来了吗
Priya's in town?
对  为了工作的事
Yeah, some work thing.
我妈好像觉得伯纳黛特
Anyway, my mother seems to think that Bernadette...
等下  普丽娅啥时候来的
Hold on. When did Priya get here?
不知道  几天前吧
I don't know. A couple of days ago.
问题是 伯纳黛特不喜欢我每天
The thing is, Bernadette doesn't like that I have to take care
照顾我妈  我妈又不信任伯纳黛特
of my mother, and my mother doesn't trust Bernadette...
嗯  确实很难办
Yeah, that's a real pickle.
拜拜
Bye.
别担心
Don't worry.
作为你排名第三的好朋友
As your tertiary friend,
我愿意挺身而出安慰你
I am prepared to step in and comfort you.
其实用不着这样
That's not really necessary.
不行不行  我来把茶泡好
No, no. I'll finish making the tea,
你继续自说自话地
while you narcissistically ramble on
倒那什么乱七八糟的苦水吧
about whatever's troubling you.
多谢
Thanks.
这就是排在第三位的朋友的作用
That's what tertiary friends are for.
谁啊
Who is it?
莱纳德
It's Leonard.
你不能进来
You can't come in.
我就想和她说句话
I just want to talk to her.
我毙之
I forbid it.
开门吧  拉杰
Open the door, Rajesh.
我说过了
You heard me.
我毙毙之
I forbidded it.
"毙毙之"
"Forbidded" it?
"吡毙之"
"Forbaded" it?
给我让开
Get out of the way.
你来做什么
What are you doing here?
你又是来做什么
我在洛杉矶有点公事
I have business in Los Angeles.
为什么不给我打电话
Why didn't you call?
显然啊  她在暗示你
Clearly, she was sending you a message
滚远点  迈克同学
to take a hike, Mike.
不好意思  我想过给你打电话
I'm sorry. I thought about calling,
但我不知道和你再见面到底合不合适
but I just wasn't sure if seeing you was such a good idea.
我懂  上次我有些太着急了
I know. Last time I came on too strong.
咱俩能单独聊聊吗
Can we talk in private?
-不行  -行啊
- No! - Sure.
一个单身女人私下招待男性
It's completely inappropriate for a single woman
这实在太荒唐了
to entertain a man in private.
要是你俩非得聊的话  就在沙发上聊
If you insist on talking, you must do it on the couch!
好吧  你俩可以在卧室里聊
All right, you may talk in the bedroom,
但是我要求你们不许关门
but I want this door to remain open!
好吧  这次让你关门
All right, just this once you may close the door.
但你给我记住  我就在外面
But keep in mind I'll be right out here
监视你俩的动向
monitoring the situation!
该死
Oh, damn it.
莱纳德  听到这条留言后请速回电
Leonard, when you get this message, call me.
普丽娅  我是你哥
Priya, this is your brother.
听到留言后请让莱纳德查收他的语音信箱
When you get this, tell Leonard to check his voicemail.
你今晚还住我们那儿吗
Would you be sleeping over again this evening?
因为我们很欢迎你
Because you're welcome to.
承蒙美意  但是我自己有计划
That's very nice of you, but I made other plans.
你只要记得只要你需要一位
Well, just keep in mind that should you ever need
略显冷淡的第三好的朋友
a slightly apathetic tertiary friend,
我时刻准备着
I stand at the ready.
嗨  霍华德  嗨  谢尔顿
Hi, Howard. Hi, Sheldon.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hello. - Hey.
你俩为啥牵着手
Why are you holding hands?
我禁止你俩牵手
I forbid you to hold hands.
拉杰  你知道莱纳德和我一起过夜了
Rajesh, you know Leonard and I spent the night together.
对  但是你俩只是睡觉而已
Yeah, but you were just sleeping,
因为我禁子你俩做爱了
because I forboded you to have sex.
应该是"禁止"
The word is "forbade""
你确定吗  听起来怪怪的
You sure? That doesn't sound right.
听着  拉杰  莱纳德和我已经决定
Listen, Rajesh, Leonard and I have decided
重拾旧情了
to see each other again,
你不可以决定
and you don't get to tell me
我该和谁拍拖
who I can and can't have a relationship with.
其实  他可以
Actually, he can.
印度的《摩奴法典》对这类问题有明确规定
The Hindu Code of Manu is very clear in these matters.
如果一个女人的父亲不在
If a woman's father is not around,
那么控制她基本欲望的责任
the duty of controlling her base desires falls
就落在了她最亲的男性亲属身上  也就是拉杰
to the closest male member of her family, in this case, Raj.
法典还规定
The code also states
如果她违背了的话  她下辈子将
that if she disobeys, she will be reborn
"投胎为豺  疾病缠身"
"in the womb of a jackal and tormented by diseases."
如果这是真的
If true,
考虑到奖品只是莱纳德
that seems like an awfully large gamble
你这个赌注貌似下得大了点
given that the prize is Leonard.
就是这样  普丽娅  我们是印度人
There it is, Priya. We're Indian.
就信这些玩意
We believe this stuff.
我觉得法典上还说  如果你吃牛肉了
I think it also says that if you eat beef,
就得和母牛一起住三个月
you need to live with cows for three months
天天喝牛尿
and drink their urine.
良莠参半  不可全信
Some of it makes sense, some of it's crazy.
我是说  你不能和莱纳德在一起
My point is, you can't go out with Leonard.
谁不能和莱纳德在一起
Who can't go out with Leonard?
我妹妹
My sister.
佩妮  这位是拉杰的妹妹  普丽娅
Penny, this is Raj's sister, Priya.
很高兴见到你
It's very nice to meet you.
哦  我也是
Oh, yeah, you, too.
普丽娅  如果你觉得有些紧张或者尴尬
Priya, if you're experiencing any tension or awkwardness,
很可能是因为莱纳德和佩妮以前曾经
it may stem from the fact that Leonard and Penny used to--
用霍华德的话来说叫做"赤裸共舞"
if I may quote Howard-- "do the dance with no pants."
谢尔顿
Sheldon!
你非得这么说吗
Really?
伯纳黛特  我能跟你说句话吗
Hey, Bernadette, can I talk to you for a second?
好
Sure.
佩妮  作为莱纳德曾经的恋人  你和他
Penny, you became disenchanted with Leonard
分手了
as a lover.
能不能跟我妹妹说说是为啥
Would you please tell my sister why?
跟你说哈  我妈要去棕榈泉市
Listen, my mom's going to Palm Springs
拜访她妹妹
to visit her sister.
我就有整整两个晚上
That's two whole nights in a row I can sleep over
能陪着你到天亮了
with you all the way to morning.
除非沙漠的干旱气候让她鼻窦干得厉害
Unless the desert air dries out her sinuses,
那样的话我就得扛着
in which case I'll have to schlep out there
庞大的增湿器赶过去
with the big humidifier.
就这样吗
That's it?
这就是解决咱俩这些问题的妙招吗
That's your big solution to all of our problems?
趁你妈不注意  我们才得两晌贪欢
If your mom's nose holds up, we get two nights together?
这不很美妙吗
Isn't that great?
不  并不好
No, it's not great.
你得作出选择  要我还是你妈
You need to make a choice.Me or your mother.
回答错误
Wrong answer.
不  等等
No, wait.
我还没说完
You didn't let me finish.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
我尽最快速度赶来了
I came as quickly as I could.
好的
Okay.
为什么
Why?
当然是赶来安慰你
To comfort you, of course.
谢尔顿说了莱纳德跟拉杰妹妹约会的事
Sheldon told me about Leonard dating Rajesh's sister.
所以我赶到这里
So I high-tailed it over here
来安慰你破碎的心
to pick up the pieces of your broken heart.
艾米  我没事
Amy, I'm fine.
你不用在我面前逞强的
You don't have to be strong for me.
我们来谈谈普丽娅那偷男人的婊子
Now let's talk about Priya, that man-stealing bitch.
什么
What?
在这样的情况下
In situations like this,
闺蜜经常都一起声讨小三的
best girlfriends are often catty about the other woman.
真的  我对莱纳德和普丽娅的事毫不伤心
Really, I am not upset about Leonard and Priya.
那你可能是并不清楚是怎么回事
Oh. Then perhaps you don't understand what's going on.
你的前男友另找了
Your former boyfriend has replaced you
一个看上去非常相配的女友
with what appears to be a very suitable mate.
可以说比你更相配得多
Arguably much more suitable than you.
好吧  那对他来说不错啊
Oh. Well, good for him.
你说"更相配"是什么意思
Hey, what do you mean, "More suitable"?
佩妮  虽然你的第二性征
Well, granted, Penny, your secondary sexual characteristics
相当明显
are reasonably bodacious.
但普丽娅有高学历
but Priya is highly educated,
她是成熟的专业人员  她们的文化中
she's an accomplished professional,she comes from the culture
甚至还有性爱宝典
that literally wrote the book on neat ways to have sex.
而你  只是社区大学辍学生
Whereas you, on the other hand, are a community college dropout
你们那的文化中  只有如何把牛推倒的书
who comes from the culture that wrote the book on tipping cows.
好吧  我听懂了
Yeah. Okay, I got it. I got it.
那些都是什么
So... what is all that stuff?
这是个便携式脑电波机
This is a portable electroencephalogram.
我正在做关于情绪和大脑活动的研究
I'm doing research on emotions and brain activity.
所以你哭的时候
So when you start crying,
我能看到你大脑的哪一区域被激活
I can see which region of the brain is activated.
然后我就刺激猕猴大脑中
Then I'm going to stimulate the analogous area
相似区域  看它是否也会哭
in the brain of a rhesus monkey and see if he cries.
很酷吧
Cool, huh?
我选你
I choose you.
真的吗
Really?
对  我搬出了我妈家
Yep. I moved out of my mother's house.
切断了束缚  我是你的了
Cord is cut.I'm all yours.
你告诉她时  她怎么说
What did she say when you told her?
不知道  她还没回我的电邮
I don't know. She hasn't responded to my email yet.
太好了
This is so great.
我爱你  霍华德
I love you, Howard.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
晚饭吃什么
So what's for dinner?
我家里没什么东西吃
Well, I don't really have much of anything in the house.
没事
That's fine.
不如先去我们的卧室做点好事
Why don't we go fool around in our bedroom?
然后你可以去买东西
And then you can go shopping.
我想吃完后  我们去看个早场电影吧
I thought maybe after we eat, we could see an early movie.
好啊
I'd love that.
我喜欢你说"好啊"的口音
I love the way you say, "I'd love that."
哥也是这么说的
She says it the same way I do.
好啊
"I'd love that."
印度人人都这么说  没什么了不起的
Everybody in India says it that way.It's not a big deal.
拉杰  别这么幼稚
Rajesh, don't be a child.
我没在耍幼稚
I'm not being a child.
莱纳德  我对天发誓
Leonard, I swear to God,
你姐姐要是来这
if your sister ever comes to town,
我也会好好"关照"她的
I shall have my way with her.
我姐姐38岁已婚
My sister's 38 and married.
模仿莎士比亚句式
那就让霍夫斯塔德家族蒙受更多耻辱
All the more shame that will fall upon the house of Hofstadter.
我好像闻到了披萨味
Ooh, I thought I smelled pizza.
太了不起了
That's remarkable.
要是意大利辣香肠是爆炸物
If pepperoni were an explosive substance,
你就可以取代国家机场的德国牧羊犬了
you could replace German shepherds at our nation's airports.
你好  你是佩妮对吧
Hi. Penny, right?
对  你好  抱歉
Oh, yes. H-Hi. I'm sorry.
我不知道你们有客人  不想来打扰
I didn't know you had company. I don't want to impose.
不  你这不是打扰
No, no. It's not an imposition.
此时在我们的生态系统中  你就相当于千鸟
At this point, in our ecosystem, you are akin to the plover,
千鸟又叫牙签鸟  常充当鳄鱼牙签的角色
一种小型净化鸟类  从鳄鱼的牙缝间
a small scavenging bird that eats extra food
吃掉多余的食物
from between the teeth of crocodiles.
请飞到我们张开的咽喉  尽情享用吧
Please, fly into our open maw, and have at it.
要不是我冰箱就剩一瓶小苏打
If I had more than a box of baking soda in my refrigerator,
我肯定不吃这嗟来之食
I wouldn't have to take that.
嗨  闺蜜
Hi, bestie.
嗨
Hi.
普丽娅  你是律师  对吧
So, um, Priya, you're a lawyer, right?
我懂  很无聊是吧
I know. Pretty boring, huh?
拜托  一点都不无聊
Oh, come on. It's not boring at all.
她正在帮助建立一个二级市场
She's currently helping set up a secondary derivative market
以便海外汽车公司巩固其投资
which would allow overseas car firms to hedge their investments
以对抗电池技术的潜在进步
against potential advancements in battery technology.
谢谢你  莱纳德
Thank you, Leonard.
让我的工作听着一点都不无聊了
That doesn't make it sound boring at all.
抱歉...
I'm sorry , but...
你还好吧
So, how you holding up?
我没事
I'm fine.
开什么玩笑  她那么动人
Oh, who are you kidding? She's breathtaking.
佩妮
So, Penny,
莱纳德跟我说  你是个演员
Leonard tells me you're an actress.
这工作肯定相当令人兴奋吧
That must be pretty exciting.
对  是挺棒的
Oh, yeah, yeah. It's real great.
今天我开车去范奈司试镜
Today I drove to Van Nuys for an audition
我原以为是一个猫食的广告
I thought was going to be for a cat food commercial.
到那才发现是黄片
Turned out to be porn.
你有幸参演吗
Did you get the part?
我连试镜都没试
I didn't do the audition.
鉴于你岌岌可危的职业生涯
Given the state of your career,
你还能挑三拣四的吗
can you really afford to be picky?
我在剑桥的时候上过表演课
I took acting classes when I was at Cambridge.
我超爱的
I loved it.
我们当时教的是《驯悍记》[莎士比亚著名喜剧]
We did Taming of the Shrew.
哇  我超爱《驯悍记》
Oh, wow. I love Taming of the Shrew.
我高中的时候还写过一篇论文呢
I did a paper on it in high school.
"谁不知道黄蜂的刺是在什么地方
"Who knows not where a wasp does wear his sting?
在尾巴上"
In his tail."
-"在舌头上"  -"谁的舌头"
- "In his tongue" - "Whose tongue?"
"你的  如果你谈论的是尾巴
"Yours, if you talk of tails,
保重啦"
and so farewell."
"什么  我的舌头在你的尾巴上"
"What, with my tongue in your tail?"
真后悔之前我对她做出这么恶毒的评价
I'm regretting my earlier cattiness.
她绝对是个可人儿
She is an absolute delight.
爽
Wow.
爽死了
Wow, indeed.
真不敢相信我们终于住在一起了
I can't believe we're finally living together.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道什么能让这一刻更加完美吗
You know what would make this moment perfect?
什么
What?
零食  你有奶酪棒吗
A little snack. You got any string cheese?
没有  我可能有些干酪
No. I-I might have some cheddar.
那个不好
Not as good.
拼不成绳子
You can't make strings with it.
记得提醒我把它加入你的购物清单
Remind me to put it on your shopping list.
好吧
Okay.
你有低敏配方的洗衣粉吗
You have hypo-allergenic detergent?
没有
No.
那这个也要买哦
Better put it on the list.
如果你用普通的肥皂帮我洗内内
If you wash my underwear with regular soap,
我的屁屁会长小红点
I get little red bumps on my tuchus.
等等
Wait a second.
我还要帮你洗衣服
I'm doing your laundry?
拜托  宝贝  衣服又不会自己跳进洗衣机
Well, honey, it's not gonna do itself.
差点忘了
Oh, before I forget,
明天早上你得开车送我去看牙医
tomorrow morning, you're driving me to the dentist.
我一定要载你去吗
I have to take you?
现在不是一定要你做  而是你必须要做
You don't have to take me. You get to take me.
慢着  你的意思是
Wait a minute. Are you telling me
你妈妈通常都带你去看牙医吗
your mother usually takes you to the dentist?
这有什么奇怪的
It's not weird.
诊所里有很多小孩都是妈妈陪着来的
There's lots of kids there with their moms.
真让人难以置信
I can't believe this.
为什么  多有爱呀
What? It's fun.
如果我没有蛀牙
If I have no cavities,
检查过后  我们就去大餐一顿
afterwards, we go out for a treat.
够了  霍华德
All right, Howard,
有件事我必须得跟你直说
let's get something straight right now.
我不会像你妈一样照顾你的
I'm not going to be your mother.
喂  喂  喂
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
此话怎讲
Where did that come from?
谁啊
Who's that?!
是性侵者吗
Is it a sex criminal?!
妈  在你面前谁都硬不起来
Nobody wants to do that to you, Ma!
你死去哪里了
Where were you?!
你没看见我的电子邮件吗
Didn't you read my email?!
你也知道我不会开那破电脑
You know I can't turn on that ferkakta computer!
我给你留了点鸡胸肉在厨房柜台上
I left you some brisket on the kitchen counter!
谢谢
Thank you!
吃完记得用牙线剔干净
Remember to floss after.
明天早上我们得去看牙医
We have the dentist in the morning!
有事吗
Oh, hey. What's up?
我只是来看看你怎么样
I just wanted to check in on you.
为什么
Why?
这是最恰当不过的事情
It seems like the appropriate thing to do
因为当自己好朋友发现自己被
when one's best friend finds herself replaced
一个聪明美丽的女人所取代
by a smart, beautiful woman
而她如同温顺的孟加拉母老虎  有一种蓄势待发的性欲
with the smoldering sexuality of a crouched Bengal tiger.
我跟你说过  我没事
I already told you, I'm okay with it.
我是说  我甚至于还很高兴
I mean, if anything, I'm quite pleased
莱纳德找到了
that Leonard has found someone
能让他开心的人
that makes him so happy.
没事的  没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在先把这些电极贴上
Now, let's get these electrodes attached
看看你的小脑袋里到底哪部分让你哭泣
and see what's going on in that pretty little noggin of yours.
好的
Okay.
我闻到中国菜的味道
I smell Chinese food.
其实是泰国菜
It's actually Thai.
你的嗅觉下降了
You're slipping.
莱纳德和普丽娅在吗
Are Leonard and Priya here?
他们去卡达利娜岛度周末了[全美最漂亮的小岛]
They went to Catalina for the weekend.
拉杰呢
Oh. Where's Raj?
在家  远程禁止他们去
At home, forbidding it.
霍华德呢
How about Howard?
据说他的母亲
I'm given to understand
把他禁足了  防止他偷跑
his mother grounded him for running away.
好吧
Oh, okay.
那就剩咱俩了  对吧
Well, I guess it's just the two of us, huh?
事实上  是剩咱三个
Actually, it's the three of us.
你好啊  闺蜜
What up, bestie?
好消息
Good news.
多亏了你  我才能成功把恒河猴弄哭
Thanks to you, I was able to make a rhesus monkey cry
就像那种蓄意煽情的情感类节目主持人一样
like a disgraced televangelist.
不错
Great.
那你感觉好点了吗
So, you feeling better?
还没有
Not really.
谢尔顿  你的客人心情不好
Sheldon, you have a guest who's upset.
知道了  我去倒茶
Right. I'll make tea.
亲爱的  没关系  我不需要
Sweetie, it's okay. I don't want tea.
抱歉  你没得选择
I'm sorry. It's not optional.